superbuytires.com 2008-06-18

# Superbuytires.com Privacy Policy

Your privacy is a priority to us, we have provided this detailed policy statement about privacy and information dissemination practices related to Super Buy Tires products. Our website visitors may enjoy many of our features and products we offer without providing any personal information. 

**Collection & Use ** **Information** **:**

(A) Super Buy Tires website forms may ask for contact and demographic information. This information is not shared or sold to anyone. It is solely used to send news about our products or promotional sales. In addition, demographic information may be used to customize the display of our website to you by showing content that we think may be of interest to you based on previous visits. You will be able to opt-out of any e-mails.

(B) Your browser offers "cookies" which - if you allow their use - store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our website. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. Also, when you re-visit our website, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. Cookies do not give us personal data unless you specifically give us additional information. Our website is viewable even if you have disabled the cookie function within your Web browser. Some advanced features use cookies to assist in keeping track of your location within the site in order to provide navigational trails and similar navigational features. These cookies are not used to personally identify your surfing patterns, and are merely used to provide navigation links. Disabling your cookies simply means that some of these features will not have custom navigation available to you.

(C) Some of the banner ads displayed in our website are provided by outside companies. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, the cookies associated with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you.

**Sharing & Disclosure Information : **

Certain informationsuch as your e-mailis not disclosed in any form whatsoever to any outside party. While we will primarily use your email address to contact you when we have new offers or special discounts on our products, you will be able to opt-out of these types of e-mails. 

** Terms of Use:**  When you register to our dealer website, you agree on receiving information on our products (wheels and tires, etc.) by email newsletters and Super Buy Tires will use your information as stated in the policies above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Super Buy Tires welcomes your questions and comments.

** If you have any other questions about our privacy policy, please contact Super Buy Tires, Inc   
at  [ privacypolicy@superbuytires.com](mailto:privacypolicy@superbuytires.com)   
or by calling 1-562-630-5848.  
 **
